JUSTINA CHAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

0432415285 | chanlaisumjustina@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/justina-chan/

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Triflex Projects

08/2021 - 03/2022

- Developed software using Java, PHP, and all the Microsoft Power Platform technologies
- Analyzed existing interfaces to detect user pain points
- Developed and implemented performance improvement strategies and plans to promote continuous improvement.
- Assist project manager with project management documents
- Integrated several different APIs such as Xero to the framework.
- Developed team communications and information for meetings.
- Participation in daily stand-ups and weekly reports.

Tools and Technologies

Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ IDEA, Docker, PHP, Java, JSON

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER & TECHNICAL SUPPORT

Climb Holding

08/2021 -12/2021

- Lead the architecture and development of one new PowerApps application for office automation systems.
- Optimizing workflow and business processes and improving internal communication and working efficiency.
- Assisted the project manager in establishing the project plan by evaluating the workload and estimations
- Communicated with product managers and UX designers to translate project requirements and business objectives into polished user interfaces.
- Participated in continuous improvement by weekly meetings, generating suggestions, engaging in problem-solving activities to support teamwork.

Tools and Technologies

all the Microsoft Power Platform technologies, including -PowerApps, Power Automate, Power BI, PowerApps Portals, Dataverse, Java, PHP, JSON,

SUMMARY

Innovative tech and business mind with more than 2 years of experience working as a software developer.

Capable of working with a variety of technology and workplaces. Valuable team member which worked with many professionals throughout different fields. Extensive experience with web development, front, and backend. Very adaptable and fast learner with unique ideas and contributions to businesses.

EDUCATION

03/2020 -09/2021

James Cook University
Bachelor of Information Technology

01/2019 -02/2020

Queensland University
of Technology
Diploma of Information Technology

SKILLS

- Technical Skills
- → .NET, C#
- → HTML, CSS, JavaScript (ES6[^]), SEO
- → WordPress
- → SQL. Dataverse
- → Microservices, PowerApp, Power Automate, Power BI
- → Git
- Personal Skills
- → UX and result oriented
- → Self-taught and open-minded
- ullet ightarrow Fluent English and Native Chinese

JUSTINA CHAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

BUSINESS EXPERIENCE

FRANCHISE OWNER

CarePlus Cleaning Solutions

08/2020 - Present

- Oversaw the daily operations of the business.
- · Performed office and management duties.
- Performed hiring, firing, and managing of employees.
- Managed marketing, bookkeeping, payroll, and advertising functions.
- Studied the industry market and kept abreast of new trends.

INTERNSHIPS

INTERNSHIP - ADMINISTRATION

Climb Holding

07/2021 -08/2021

- Screened and transferred incoming calls, took down messages, and transmitted information and documents to internal personnel.
- Devised and implemented improvements to reporting procedures.
- Provide ideas to improve the work environment and organize team-building activities.

INTERNSHIP PROJECTS

Casphone

05/2021 - 08/2021

- Understanding the customer's need and providing a project plan.
- Worked on projects using knowledge gained in classes to put together recommendations for issues.
- Developed and maintained courteous and effective working relationships.
- Participation in weekly meetings with the company owner.

JUSTINA CHAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROJECTS

WEB DESIGN AND DEVELOP PROJECTS

Ihealth beauty

012/2021 - 03/2022

- Successful developed multilingual eCommerce website
- Leveraged a strong understanding of WordPress core to manipulate admin and theme components.
- · Installed required plugins and additional coding to fit final design and functionality requirements.
- Developed and implemented SEO strategies to improve the effectiveness of marketing efforts
- Main Skills involved:
- PHP, CSS, Wordpress,

INFORMATION ARCHITECTURE AND INTERFACE DESIGN

U3A - the University of the Third Age

01/2021 -01/2021

- Create a WordPress custom theme from scratch;
- Set up the local development environment using docker and docker-compose;
- Create the git workflow and docs;
- Deploy custom-theme into WordPress;
- Main Skills involved:
- PHP, CSS, Wordpress, Docker, Docker-compose

WEB DESIGN AND DEVELOP PROJECTS

First Met Café

011/2020 - 12/2020

- Designed user interface and integrated it into the content management system to meet client specifications.
- Participation and organizing meetings with the company owner.
- Analyzed and summarized the customer requirements
- Main Skills involved:
- PHP, CSS, Wordpress,

INTERNATIONAL TRADE RESEARCH PROJECT

Practera

007/2020 - 07/2020

- Created and implemented procedures to obtain required information and support research goals.
- Took an active role in meetings, engaging with all parties and transcribing detailed notes of plans, decisions, and options discussed.
- completed the project and fulfill the requirement within 2 weeks